The rain painted the streets of Paris in silvery strokes, shimmering under dim lantern light.
A woman clutching her umbrella paused near a bridge.
Her eyes meet his, a man standing alone, drenched, staring into the Seine.
You're lost, aren't you? she asked, her voice soft yet wary.
He smiled faintly, but something about him felt off.
Their conversation unfolded slowly, as if the city itself were listening.
They shared stories, hers a tourist exploring Paris for the first time, his, a writer searching
for inspiration.
But as she leaned closer, her gaze landed on the edge of his sleeve, dark stains smeared
and unsettling.
Is that blood? she whispered.
He froze.
The air thickened, suffocating.
His smile faded, revealing something darker.
You shouldn't have noticed that.
Her heart raced.
Footsteps echoed in the distance.
She turned to run, but his grip closed around her wrist like a vice.
Paris has secrets, he murmured, his voice low and icy.
And you just stumbled into mine.
The lanterns flickered, their glow faltering, as the city seemed to close around them.